{
    "id": "4fbbced4dae64556820454ce5420e6ca",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………… anything for hours.",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with the time expressions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "am not eating",
                "haven't eaten",
                "didn't eat"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I believe that professionals ……………………. doctors and teachers are more useful than actors or singers.",
            "description": "Either like or such as can be used to give examples. ",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as",
                "such as",
                "Either like or such as"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The child …………………… sits in that corner is my nephew.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………… behave.",
            "description": "All of these expressions indicate ideas such as obligation and necessity. ",
            "answers": [
                "ought to",
                "should",
                "must",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "You ......................... quit the job.",
            "description": "Must is a modal auxiliary. Questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "do not must",
                "must not to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ……………………… friends.",
            "description": "Not any means the same as no. ",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "any",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I called him in the morning but he didn’t ……………………. the phone.",
            "description": "Use the bare infinitive (v1) after do, does and did.",
            "answers": [
                "answer",
                "answered",
                "answering"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t ……………………… agree with this view.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite",
                "quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The situation is getting ……………………day by day.",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worser",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am now here ……………………. my mom.",
            "description": "Because of is a preposition. It is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Work …………………… the best of your ability.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I went home …………………….. I was bored.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. It is used to connect two clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}